teconce.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy - Powerful Niche Based WordPress

Teconce takes data privacy very seriously and recognises the importance of protecting and respecting your personal data. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect, how we use that information, to whom we pass the information, your rights and key contact information.

## Overview

To provide you with the WordPress services we need to collect information about you. Our aim is not to be intrusive, and we won’t ask you unnecessary questions. Any information we receive about you will be subject to strict controls to minimize the risk of misuse – including unauthorized access to, or disclosure of, your personal data.

If you have concerns about any of the terms of this Privacy Policy, please email us so that we can provide further information.

## The Information We Collect

You may provide us with information by filling in forms on our website, our payment gateways’ websites or by corresponding with us via email or otherwise.

This includes information you provide when you browse our website, register for an account, purchase from us, and when you contact us for other reasons.

### Information You Provide to Us

On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Your Name
  * Billing address
  * Credit card/payment details
  * Email address
  * Website address
  * Username and password

Additionally we may also collect the following information:

  * Location and traffic data (including IP address and browser type) if you place an order, or if we need to estimate taxes and shipping costs based on your location.
  * Product pages visited and content viewed while your session is active.
  * Your comments and product reviews if you choose to leave them on our website.
  * Account email/password to allow you to access your account if you have one.
  * If you choose to create an account with us, your name, address, and email address, which will be used to populate the checkout for future orders.

### When We Communicate

When you communicate with us for customer service or other purposes, including by email or using other methods, we retain that information and our responses to you.

**Information We Collect When You Use Our Website**  
When you arrive at or leave the Teconce website, we receive the web address of the site that you came from or are going to.

While you are using our site we collect information on the services you search for or view, page response times and length of visits to specific pages, and methods used to browse away from the page.

We collect information about the device you are using, such as the type of device, operating system and platform, the type and version of browser, browser plug-in types and versions, the times you access our website/app and the time zone setting, mobile network information and unique device identifier.

### How We Use Information

Our primary purpose in collecting your information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient and customised experience. By submitting your information to Teconce, you agree that we may use your information for the following purposes:

**Fulfilling Your Requests**  
We use return e-mail addresses to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us, including the provision of WordPress themes and plugins.

**Communication and Customer Service**  
We communicate with our users on a regular basis via email to provide requested services and help you manage your account. These activities include:

**Responding to requests for customer service**  
Confirming information concerning a user’s identity, business or account activity  
Resolving customer complaints  
We use your email address to:

**Confirm your opening of a Teconce account**  
Send you notice of any purchases that you make with Teconce  
Send you information about important changes to our products and services, including notice of any times that our services may not be available Send notices and other disclosures required by law  
Users cannot opt out of these communications, but they will be primarily service-oriented rather than promotional.  
As we are obligated to send these communications to current customers, if you do not wish to receive these communications at all, then, unfortunately, you must close your account.

**Marketing**  
We also use your email address to send you other types of communications that you can control, including information about new themes, customer surveys and special promotions. These communications are to:

Provide you with information about services we offer that are similar to those that you have already enquired about or purchased  
Provide news about the WordPress industry, marketing and advertising messages, updates on the services we offer, and promotional offers based on your activities  
Tell you about new products and features we are developing that you may find useful

## How the information is stored

We save your personal information in our database in order to improve our Web site’s and user experience and in accordance with our Terms & Conditions. If you wish that your personal information be permanently deleted from our database when you stop using our Services, please notify us at hello@teconce.com.

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

## Cookies Policy

Teconce is using cookies to improve your experience of our Website. When you visit our Website, Teconce servers send a cookie to your web browser. You can delete these cookies at any time. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify an individual. Cookies merely recognize the web browser. Please refer to our [Cookie Policy](https://teconce.com/gdpr-policy/) for more information.
